<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="a_negative">[Å, ñéĝåţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="a_positive">[Å, þöšîţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="ab_negative">[Å Б ñéĝåţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="ab_positive">[Å Б þöšîţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="abminus">[ÅБ- one]</string>
    <string name="abplus">[ÅБ+ one]</string>
    <string name="account_error_body_try_again">[Ţĥîš çöûļð бé å ţémþöŕåŕý þŕöбļém. Ţŕý åĝåîñ öŕ çöññéçţ ţö åñöţĥéŕ Ŵî-Fî ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="account_error_description_no_network">"[Ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåvé å ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="account_error_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šîĝñ îñ one two]"</string>
    <string name="account_login_button_text">[Çöñţîñûé åš ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_not_supported_dialog_message">"[Åççöûñţ måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ îšñ'ţ šûþþöŕţéð. Ţö ûšé Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý, þļéåšé çĥööšé åñöţĥéŕ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]"</string>
    <string name="account_not_supported_dialog_title">[Åççöûñţ ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="account_selection_accessibility">[Šéļéçţ åççöûñţ: ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="account_sign_in_button_text">[Šîĝñ îñ one]</string>
    <string name="accounts_switch_accounts">[Šŵîţçĥ åççöûñţš one two]</string>
    <string name="add_emergency_contact">[Åðð çöñţåçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="add_emergency_info_after_setup">[Ĝö бåçķ ţö ƒîñîšĥ šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ þĥöñé. Ýöû çåñ åðð éméŕĝéñçý îñƒö åƒţéŕ šéţûþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="address">[Åððŕéšš one]</string>
    <string name="address_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="affirm_call_count_down_negative_keyword_prompt">[Ýöû šåîð “ᐅ%sᐊ”. Éméŕĝéñçý çåļļ çåñçéļļéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="affirm_crash_check_negative_keyword_prompt">[Ýöû šåîð “ᐅ%sᐊ”. Éméŕĝéñçý çåļļ çåñçéļļéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="affirm_crash_check_positive_keyword_prompt">[Ýöû šåîð “ᐅ%1$sᐊ”. Çåļļîñĝ ᐅ%2$sᐊ ñöŵ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="airplane_mode_on_dialog_message">[Ţö ûšé ᐅ%1$sᐊ, ţûŕñ öƒƒ åîŕþļåñé möðé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="airplane_mode_on_dialog_title">[Åîŕþļåñé möðé îš öñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="allergies">[Åļļéŕĝîéš one two]</string>
    <string name="allergies_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="aminus">[Å- one]</string>
    <string name="aplus">[Å+ one]</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_label">[Šåƒéţý one]</string>
    <string name="app_name">[Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý one two]</string>
    <string name="app_update_card_body_text">"[Ûþðåţé Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý ţö šéé ŵĥåţ'š ñéŵ one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="app_update_card_title">[Ĝéţ ţĥé ļåţéšţ véŕšîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="b_negative">[Б ñéĝåţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="b_positive">[Б þöšîţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="blood_type">[Бļööð ţýþé one two]</string>
    <string name="blood_type_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="bminus">[Б- one]</string>
    <string name="bplus">[Б+ one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_continue">[Çöñţîñûé one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_next">[Ñéxţ one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_settings">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_skip">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_start">[Šţåŕţ one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_turn_off">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="button_text_turn_on">[Ţûŕñ öñ one]</string>
    <string name="call_count_down_voice_prompt">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţéð. Çåļļîñĝ ᐅ%1$sᐊ åûţömåţîçåļļý îñ ᐅ%2$dᐊ šéçöñðš. Šåý ᐅ%3$sᐊ ţö šţöþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="call_emergency_button_content_description">[Çåļļ ᐅ%sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="call_emergency_button_subtext">[Éméŕĝéñçý one two]</string>
    <string name="call_the_contact">[Çåļļ ţĥé çöñţåçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_promo_card_content_description">[Ðîšmîšš çåŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="cannot_switch_accounts_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šŵîţçĥ åççöûñţ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="cant_start_one_time_sharing_card_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šţåŕţ éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="car_crash_consent_update_content_v1">"If you're in a crash, new crash data will be sent to %s. Tap to learn more."</string>
    <string name="car_crash_consent_update_notification_channel_name">Car crash detection consent updates</string>
    <string name="car_crash_consent_update_title_v1">Update to car crash detection</string>
    <string name="car_crash_detection_feature_title_text">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_enable_failed_message">"[Çåñ'ţ ţûŕñ öñ çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="car_crash_feature_no_longer_suspended_generic_content_text">[Ţåþ ƒöŕ šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_feature_no_longer_suspended_title">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ îš бåçķ öñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_feature_state_updates_notification_channel_name">Car crash detection status updates</string>
    <string name="car_crash_feature_suspended_generic_content_text">[Ţåþ ţö šéé ðéţåîļš îñ çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_feature_suspended_title">"[Çåñ'ţ ðéţéçţ çåŕ çŕåšĥéš one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="car_crash_onboarding_card_body_text">[Ĝéţ ĥéļþ çåļļîñĝ ᐅ%1$sᐊ åƒţéŕ å çŕåšĥ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_onboarding_card_secondary_btn_text">[Ţŕý å ðémö one two]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_onboarding_card_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="car_crash_settings_failed_to_load_message">"[Çåñ'ţ ļöåð çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="car_crash_turn_off_warning_dialog_content">"[Ýöû ŵöñ'ţ бé åбļé ţö ţûŕñ ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé öñ åĝåîñ ûñţîļ ýöû'ŕé îñ å šûþþöŕţéð çöûñţŕý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]"</string>
    <string name="car_crash_turn_off_warning_dialog_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="change_setting_link">[Çĥåñĝé šéţţîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="choose_account_dialog_title">[Çĥööšé åççöûñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="close_button_content_description">[Çļöšé ðémö one two]</string>
    <string name="confirm_emergency_call_text">[Ţåþ åĝåîñ ţö çåļļ ᐅ%sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="contacts_empty_state_preference_title">[Ñö îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="count_down_title_text">[Îƒ ñö ŕéšþöñšé, çåļļîñĝ ᐅ%sᐊ ţö ŕéþöŕţ çåŕ çŕåšĥ îñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="crash_check_demo_instructions_text">"[Ţåþ Î'm ÖĶ ţö ĝö ţö ţĥé ñéxţ šţéþ. Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ŕéšþöñð, ţĥé ðémö åšķš îƒ ýöû'ŕé öķåý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="crash_check_title">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="crash_check_voice_prompt">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţéð. Šåý “ᐅ%1$sᐊ” ţö çåļļ ᐅ%2$sᐊ ñöŵ. Öţĥéŕŵîšé, šåý “ᐅ%3$sᐊ”. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="crash_demo_alert_title_text">"[Ŵåîţ öŕ ţåþ Î'm ÖĶ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="crash_onboarding_main_image_description">[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="crash_onboarding_title_text">@string/crash_onboarding_main_image_description</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_check_user_status_body_text">[Þîxéļ vîбŕåţéš, šöûñðš åñ åļåŕm åţ måxîmûm vöļûmé, åñð åšķš îƒ ýöû ñééð ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_check_user_status_title_text">[Ŵĥéñ å çŕåšĥ îš ðéţéçţéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_emergency_alert_body_text">[Þîxéļ åţţémþţš ţö çöñţåçţ ᐅ%sᐊ ţö þŕövîðé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñð çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðåţå. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_emergency_alert_title_text">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ŕéšþöñð one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_how_it_works_body_2_text">[Ķééþ îñ mîñð, Þîxéļ måý ñöţ бé åбļé ţö ðéţéçţ åļļ çŕåšĥéš, åñð ĥîĝĥ îmþåçţ åçţîvîţîéš måý åçţîvåţé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_how_it_works_body_text">"[Þîxéļ ûšéš ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, möţîöñ šéñšöŕš, &amp; åmбîéñţ åûðîö ţö ðéţéçţ å çåŕ çŕåšĥ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]"</string>
    <string name="crash_settings_how_it_works_title_text">[Ĥöŵ îţ ŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="demo_completed_title_text">"[Ýöû'vé ŕéåçĥéð ţĥé éñð öƒ ţĥé ðémö one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="demo_intro_description_text">[Šéé åñð ĥéåŕ ŵĥåţ ĥåþþéñš ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ þĥöñé ðéţéçţš å çåŕ çŕåšĥ. Måķé šûŕé ýöûŕ vöļûmé îš ûþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="demo_intro_title_text">[Ţŕý å ðémö one two]</string>
    <string name="device_location_not_enabled_dialog_message">[Ţö ûšé ᐅ%1$sᐊ, ţûŕñ öñ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="device_location_not_enabled_dialog_title">[Ļöçåţîöñ îš öƒƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_location_off_card_body_text">[Ţûŕñ öñ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ ţö šĥåŕé ŵĥéŕé ýöû åŕé ŵîţĥ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="device_location_off_card_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="display_account_dialog_message">[Ţö éðîţ ýöûŕ šåƒéţý šéţţîñĝš ƒöŕ åñöţĥéŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ, öþéñ ţĥé Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý åþþ îñšţéåð åñð šŵîţçĥ åççöûñţš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="display_account_dialog_message_for_prompt_login">[Ţö éðîţ šåƒéţý šéţţîñĝš åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ, öþéñ ţĥé Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý åþþ åñð šîĝñ îñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="display_account_dialog_title">[Šĥöŵîñĝ îñƒö ƒöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="emergency_call_demo_title_text">[Þŕévîéŵ öƒ ᐅ%sᐊ çåļļ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="emergency_call_image_content_description">[Îmåĝé öƒ ţĥé šçŕééñ ðûŕîñĝ å ᐅ%sᐊ çåļļ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact_copying_message">[Çöñţåçţš šåvéð öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé mövéð ţö ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact_edit_notification_channel_name">[Éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţ çĥåñĝéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact_edit_notification_content_text">[Éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţ ûþðåţéð öŕ ŕémövéð. Ţåþ ţö ŕévîéŵ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact_edit_notification_title">[Çĥåñĝé ţö éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact_title">[Åðð éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contacts_footer_hide_message">"[Ţĥéšé çöñţåçţš ŵöñ'ţ бé šĥöŵñ ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš ļöçķéð.ñᐅ^1ᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="emergency_contacts_footer_message">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ åñð çåļļ ţĥéšé çöñţåçţš ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contacts_footer_message_with_period">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ åñð çåļļ ţĥéšé çöñţåçţš ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contacts_footer_show_message">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ åñð çåļļ ţĥéšé çöñţåçţš ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé.ñᐅ^1ᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="emergency_contacts_fragment_title">[Éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="emergency_count_down_demo_instructions_text">[Çĥööšé åñ öþţîöñ бý ţĥé éñð öƒ ţĥé ţîméŕ, öŕ ŵåîţ ţö šéé ŵĥåţ ĥåþþéñš ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ þĥöñé çöñţåçţš ᐅ%sᐊ öñ ýöûŕ бéĥåļƒ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="emergency_count_down_demo_title_text">[Ŵåîţ ţö þŕévîéŵ å ᐅ%sᐊ çåļļ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="emergency_info_device_only_message">[Ţĥîš îñƒö îš šåvéð öñļý öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="emergency_info_display_setting_description">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš åñð méðîçåļ îñƒö çåñ бé åççéššéð ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš ļöçķéð.ññFîŕšţ ŕéšþöñðéŕš åñð þéöþļé ŵîţĥ åççéšš ţö ýöûŕ ðévîçé çåñ åļšö ðîåļ ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty]</string>
    <string name="emergency_info_display_setting_switch_label">[Šĥöŵ ŵĥéñ ļöçķéð one two]</string>
    <string name="emergency_info_display_setting_title">[Šĥöŵ ŵĥéñ ðévîçé îš ļöçķéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="emergency_info_name">[Éméŕĝéñçý îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="expand_pref_title">[Möŕé one]</string>
    <string name="fail_add_contact">"[Çåñ'ţ šåvé ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="fail_display_contact">"[Çåñ'ţ šĥöŵ ţĥé çöñţåçţ îñ ýöûŕ çöñţåçţš åþþ. Çĥéçķ ţĥé Çöñţåçţš åþþ &amp; ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="fail_list_contacts">"[Çåñ'ţ ļîšţ ýöûŕ çöñţåçţš one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="fail_load_contact_picker">"[Çåñ'ţ ĝéţ çöñţåçţš ƒŕöm ýöûŕ Çöñţåçţš åþþ. Çĥéçķ ţĥé Çöñţåçţš åþþ &amp; ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="fail_load_contacts">"[Çåñ'ţ ļöåð çöñţåçţš. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="fail_remove_contact">"[Çåñ'ţ ŕémövé ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="failed_one_time_share_message">[Méššåĝé ñöţ šéñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="feature_demo">[Ðémöš one]</string>
    <string name="fetch_error">"[Çåñ'ţ ļöåð ýöûŕ méðîçåļ îñƒö one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="generic_error_message">[Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="get_photo_error">"[Çåñ'ţ ĝéţ ýöûŕ þĥöţö. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="get_user_info_error">"[Çåñ'ţ šĥöŵ ýöûŕ ñåmé åñð þĥöţö one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="greetings_text">[Ĥî ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="h_h">[ĥ ĥ one]</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="hh">[ĥ/ĥ one]</string>
    <string name="hidden_info_message">[Ţåþ ţö ûñļöçķ åñð vîéŵ îñƒö one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="im_okay_button_text">"[Î'm ÖĶ one]"</string>
    <string name="im_okay_dont_call_button_text">"[Î'm ÖĶ. Ðöñ'ţ çåļļ. one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="invalid_phone_number">[Îñvåļîð þĥöñé ñûmбéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="launch_app_text">[Öþéñ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="launch_app_view_description">[Öþéñ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ţö åðð îñƒö. Ţĥîš îñƒö îš åvåîļåбļé ţö åñýöñé ŵîţĥ åççéšš ţö ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_card_btn_text">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_text">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="legal_privacy_policy">[Þŕîvåçý Þöļîçý one two]</string>
    <string name="legal_terms_of_service">[Ţéŕmš öƒ Šéŕvîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="legal_tos_and_privacy">"[Бý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝŕéé ţö Ĝööĝļé'š ᐅ^1ᐊ. Ĝööĝļé'š ᐅ^2ᐊ ðéšçŕîбéš ĥöŵ ýöûŕ ðåţå îš ĥåñðļéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="loading_contacts">[Ļöåðîñĝ çöñţåçţš... one two three]</string>
    <string name="me_card_settings_summary">[Méðîçåļ îñƒö, éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="me_card_settings_title">[Éméŕĝéñçý îñƒö one two]</string>
    <string name="medical_conditions">[Méðîçåļ ñöţéš one two]</string>
    <string name="medical_conditions_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_copying_message">[Îñƒö šåvéð öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé mövéð ţö ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_empty_state_preference_summary">"[Ţåþ Éðîţ ţö åðð îñƒö ţĥåţ'š šĥöŵñ ţö ƒîŕšţ ŕéšþöñðéŕš îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="medical_info_empty_state_preference_title">[Ñö îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_footer_hide_message">"[Ţĥîš îñƒö ŵöñ'ţ бé šĥöŵñ ŵĥéñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš ļöçķéð.ñᐅ^1ᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="medical_info_footer_message">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ ţĥîš îñƒö ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_footer_message_with_period">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ ţĥîš îñƒö ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_footer_show_message">[Ţö ĥéļþ îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý, þéöþļé çåñ vîéŵ ţĥîš îñƒö ŵîţĥöûţ ûñļöçķîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé.ñᐅ^1ᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_fragment_title">[Méðîçåļ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="medical_info_title">[Åðð méðîçåļ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="medications">[Méðîçåţîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="medications_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="menu_open_source_licenses">[Öþéñ šöûŕçé ļîçéñšéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="minor_crash_button_text">[Mîñöŕ çŕåšĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="missing_permission_dialog_title">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ åççéšš ñééðéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="missing_permission_message">[Þéŕmîššîöñš ðéñîéð. Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ îš öƒƒ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="missing_permission_message_for_demo">[Þéŕmîššîöñš ðéñîéð. Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðémö ñöţ šţåŕţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="name">[Ñåmé one]</string>
    <string name="new_contact_indicator">[Ñéŵ one]</string>
    <string name="no">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="no_crash_button_text">[Ñö çŕåšĥ one]</string>
    <string name="no_crash_feedback_demo_instructions_text">[Ţö ĥéļþ Ĝööĝļé îmþŕövé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ, šĥåŕé ŵĥåţ ĥåþþéñéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="no_crash_feedback_demo_title_text">[Åðð çŕåšĥ îñƒö one two]</string>
    <string name="no_crash_feedback_title">"[Ĝļåð ýöû'ŕé ÖĶ. Ŵĥåţ ĥåþþéñéð¿ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="no_emergency_number">[Ñö éméŕĝéñçý ñûmбéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_internet_access_dialog_message">[Ţö ûšé ᐅ%1$sᐊ, ţûŕñ öñ Ŵî-Fî öŕ çĥéçķ ýöûŕ möбîļé ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="no_internet_access_dialog_title">[Ñö çöññéçţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="no_mobile_network_card_body_text">[Ţö ûšé éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ, çĥéçķ ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="no_mobile_network_card_title">[Ñö möбîļé ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_mobile_network_dialog_message">[Ţö ûšé ᐅ%1$sᐊ, çĥéçķ ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="no_mobile_network_dialog_title">[Ñö möбîļé ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_sim_card_dialog_message">[Ţö ûšé ᐅ%1$sᐊ, åðð å ŠÎM çåŕð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="no_sim_card_dialog_title">[Ñö ŠÎM çåŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="no_speech_recognizer_voice_prompt">"[Çåñ'ţ ûšé šþééçĥ ŕéçöĝñîţîöñ ţö çåļļ. Îƒ ýöû ñééð ĥéļþ, ţåþ ţĥé ᐅ%sᐊ бûţţöñ öñ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="notification_access_policy_permission_group_label">[Ðö Ñöţ Ðîšţûŕб one two]</string>
    <string name="notification_access_policy_permission_label">[åççéšš ðö ñöţ ðîšţûŕб one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="o_negative">[Ö ñéĝåţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="o_positive">[Ö þöšîţîvé one two]</string>
    <string name="ominus">[Ö- one]</string>
    <string name="one_time_share_default_message">"[Î'm îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý. Ĥéŕé'š mý ļöçåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="one_time_share_no_location_default_message">"[Î'm îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý. one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="one_time_share_notification_channel_name">[Éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="one_time_share_notification_description">[Ţåþ ţö šĥåŕé åĝåîñ ŵîţĥ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="one_time_share_notification_title">[Méššåĝé åñð ļöçåţîöñ ñöţ šéñţ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_airplane_mode_card_body_text">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ åîŕþļåñé möðé ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñð šţåţûš ûþðåţéš ŵîţĥ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_btn_text">[Šţåŕţ méššåĝé one two]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_card_btn_text_without_contacts">[Åðð çöñţåçţš one two]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_card_num_of_emergency_contacts">{NUM_CONTACTS,plural, =1{[# ÇÖÑŢÅÇŢ one two]}other{[# ÇÖÑŢÅÇŢŠ one two]}}</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_card_subtitle_with_contacts">[Îƒ ýöû ñééð ĥéļþ, qûîçķļý šéñð ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñð šţåţûš ţö ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_card_subtitle_without_contacts">"[Åðð éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš šö ýöû'ŕé ŕéåðý ţö šĥåŕé îñƒö ðûŕîñĝ çŕîţîçåļ möméñţš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_card_title">[Éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_feature_name">[éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_no_sim_card_body_text">[Åðð å ŠÎM çåŕð ţö šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñð šţåţûš ûþðåţéš ŵîţĥ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_permission_denied">[Þéŕmîššîöñš ðéñîéð. one two three]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_setup_subtitle">[Ţåþ бéļöŵ ţö éðîţ ţĥé méššåĝé. Ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ îš åţţåçĥéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="one_time_sharing_setup_title">[Šĥåŕé éméŕĝéñçý šţåţûš one two three]</string>
    <string name="open_app_button_text">[Öþéñ åþþ one]</string>
    <string name="oplus">[Ö+ one]</string>
    <string name="opt_in_button_text">"[Ýéš, Î'm îñ one two]"</string>
    <string name="opt_out_button_text">[Ñö ţĥåñķš one two]</string>
    <string name="organ_donor">[Öŕĝåñ ðöñöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="organ_donor_unknown">[Ûñķñöŵñ one]</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_for_location">[Ţö šĥåŕé ŵĥéŕé ýöû åŕé ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš, ᐅ%2$sᐊ ñééðš ᐅ%1$sᐊ åççéšš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_for_sharing">[Ţö šĥåŕé ûþðåţéš ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš, ᐅ%2$sᐊ ñééðš ᐅ%1$sᐊ åççéšš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="personal_safety_introduction_body_text">[Çĥéçķ öûţ šömé ŵåýš ţö šţåý šåƒéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="phone_type_and_phone_number">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ • ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="positive_user_response_keyword">[éméŕĝéñçý one two]</string>
    <string name="profile_tab_crash_settings_disabled_description_text">[Öƒƒ / Ţåþ ţö ĝéţ ĥéļþ çåļļîñĝ ᐅ<xliff example="911" id="emergency_services_number">ᐊᐅ%sᐊᐅ</xliff>ᐊ åƒţéŕ å çŕåšĥ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="profile_tab_crash_settings_enabled_description_text">[Öñ one]</string>
    <string name="profile_tab_crash_settings_temporarily_off_description_text">[Öƒƒ ţémþöŕåŕîļý / Ţåþ ƒöŕ ðéţåîļš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="remove">[Ŕémövé one]</string>
    <string name="remove_contact">[Ŕémövé ᐅ%1$sᐊ ƒŕöm éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš¿ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="remove_contact_icon_text">[Ŕémövé çöñţåçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="select_account_frag_subtitle">[Åðð éméŕĝéñçý çöñţåçţš, méðîçåļ îñƒö, åñð šéé ĥöŵ ýöûŕ Þîxéļ çåñ ĥéļþ ýöû îñ åñ éméŕĝéñçý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="select_account_frag_title">[Ŵéļçömé ţö ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="send_message_button_text">[Šéñð one]</string>
    <string name="set_photo_to_user_manager_error">"[Çåñ'ţ šåvé ýöûŕ þĥöţö one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="setting_summary_feature_unavailable">[Ûñåvåîļåбļé one two]</string>
    <string name="settings_activity_title">[Šéţţîñĝš one]</string>
    <string name="settings_suggestion_body">[Ļéţ ƒîŕšţ ŕéšþöñðéŕš šéé ýöûŕ îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="settings_suggestion_title">[Åðð éméŕĝéñçý îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="sign_in_card_body_text">[Šîĝñ îñ ţö ýöûŕ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ţö ûšé éméŕĝéñçý šĥåŕîñĝ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="sign_in_card_btn_text">[Šîĝñ îñ one]</string>
    <string name="sign_in_card_title">[Ðö möŕé ŵîţĥ Þéŕšöñåļ Šåƒéţý one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="specific_missing_permission_message">[Þéŕmîššîöñ ţö ᐅ%sᐊ ðéñîéð. Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ îš öƒƒ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="specific_missing_permission_message_for_demo">[Þéŕmîššîöñ ţö ᐅ%sᐊ ðéñîéð. Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðémö ñöţ šţåŕţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="start_over_demo_button_text">[Šţåŕţ övéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="successful_one_time_share_message">{CONTACTS_COUNT,plural, =1{[Méššåĝé šéñţ ţö # çöñţåçţ one two three four five six]}other{[Méššåĝé šéñţ ţö # çöñţåçţš one two three four five six]}}</string>
    <string name="suspended_link_country_text">[Šûþþöŕţéð çöûñţŕîéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="suspended_link_locale_text">[Šûþþöŕţéð ļåñĝûåĝéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_country_body_text">"[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ŵĥîļé ýöû'ŕé îñ ţĥîš çöûñţŕý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_country_title_text">[Ûñåvåîļåбļé îñ ţĥîš çöûñţŕý one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_enable_permissions_text">[Ûþðåţé þéŕmîššîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_locale_body_text">"[Çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ ðöéšñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ þĥöñé'š þŕîmåŕý ļåñĝûåĝé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_locale_title_text">[Ûñåvåîļåбļé ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ļåñĝûåĝé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_location_settings_body_text">[Ţûŕñ öñ ļöçåţîöñ ţö ûšé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_location_settings_title_text">[Ļöçåţîöñ îš öƒƒ one two]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_no_network_body_text">[Ţö ûšé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ, çĥéçķ ýöûŕ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_no_network_title_text">[Ñö möбîļé ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_no_sim_card_body_text">[Ţö ûšé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ, åðð å ŠÎM çåŕð ƒŕöm å šûþþöŕţéð çöûñţŕý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_no_sim_card_title_text">[Ñö ŠÎM çåŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_permissions_body_text">[Þļéåšé ŕé-éñåбļé mîššîñĝ þéŕmîššîöñš ţö çöñţîñûé ðéţéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_permissions_title_text">[Þéŕmîššîöñ ñééðéð ţö ðéţéçţ çŕåšĥéš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_roaming_body_text">"[Måķé šûŕé ýöû'ŕé îñ å šûþþöŕţéð çöûñţŕý, åñð ýöûŕ ŠÎM îš ƒŕöm ţĥé šåmé çöûñţŕý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_roaming_title_text">[Ûñåvåîļåбļé ŵĥîļé ŕöåmîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_unsupported_sim_card_body_text">[Ţö ûšé çåŕ çŕåšĥ ðéţéçţîöñ, ţŕý å ŠÎM çåŕð ƒŕöm å šûþþöŕţéð çöûñţŕý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="suspended_reason_unsupported_sim_card_title_text">[Ûñåvåîļåбļé ŵîţĥ ţĥîš ŠÎM one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="switch_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="switch_on">[Öñ one]</string>
    <string name="tap_pending_demo_instructions_text">[Šéé ĥöŵ ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ åñð éméŕĝéñçý îñƒö ðîšþļåý ðûŕîñĝ å ᐅ%1$sᐊ çåļļ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="tap_pending_demo_title_text">[Ţåþ ᐅ%sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="title_emergency_info">[Éméŕĝéñçý îñƒö one two]</string>
    <string name="title_other">[Öţĥéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="title_service">[Ðéţéçţîöñ &amp; åļéŕţš one two three]</string>
    <string name="title_support">[Šûþþöŕţ one]</string>
    <string name="title_try_it_now">[Ţŕý îţ ñöŵ one two]</string>
    <string name="title_watch_a_demo">[Ŵåţçĥ å vîðéö one two]</string>
    <string name="try_a_demo_button_text">[Ţŕý å ðémö one two]</string>
    <string name="update_error">"[Çåñ'ţ šåvé ýöûŕ méðîçåļ îñƒö. Ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="update_permission_btn_text">[Ûþðåţé þéŕmîššîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="use_without_an_account_button_text">[Ûšé ŵîţĥöûţ åñ åççöûñţ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="user_image_choose_photo">[Çĥööšé åñ îmåĝé one two]</string>
    <string name="user_image_photo_selector">[Šéļéçţ þĥöţö one two]</string>
    <string name="user_image_take_photo">[Ţåķé å þĥöţö one two]</string>
    <string name="user_nickname">[Ñîçķñåmé one]</string>
    <string name="user_no_response_emergency_demo_instructions_text">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ŕéšþöñð åƒţéŕ å çŕåšĥ, ýöûŕ þĥöñé çåļļš ᐅ%sᐊ öñ ýöûŕ бéĥåļƒ. Ţåþ ţĥé ðémö ţö çöñţîñûé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="user_requested_emergency_demo_instructions_text">"[Ţĥîš îš ŵĥåţ ýöû'ļļ šéé ŵĥéñ ýöû çåļļ ᐅ%sᐊ ðûŕîñĝ åñ éméŕĝéñçý. Ţåþ ţĥé ðémö ţö çöñţîñûé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]"</string>
    <string name="wait_msg">[Ĵûšţ å šéçû2026 one two]</string>
    <string name="who_to_notify_title">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_not_supported">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="yes">[Ýéš one]</string>
</resources>
