<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ĥöḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">[ÑåVîĝåţé ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">[Ḿöŕé öþţîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">[Šéé åļļ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">[Çĥööšé åñ åþþ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">[ÖFF one]</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">[ÖÑ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">[Åļţ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">[Çţŕļ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">[ðéļéţé one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">[éñţéŕ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">[Fûñçţîöñ+ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">[Ḿéţå+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">[Šĥîƒţ+ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">[šþåçé one]</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">[Šýḿ+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">[Ḿéñû+ one]</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">[Šéåŕçĥ… one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">[Çļéåŕ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">[Šéåŕçĥ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">[Šûɓḿîţ Qûéŕý one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">[νöîçé šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">[Šĥåŕé ŵîţĥ %s one two]</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">[Çöļļåþšé one two]</string>
    <string name="accept_and_continue">"[Åççéþţ &amp;  çöñţîñûé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="access_links">[Åççéšš ļîñķš one two]</string>
    <string name="access_list_of_links">[Åççéšš å ļîšţ öƒ ļîñķš one two three]</string>
    <string name="access_terms">[Åççéšš ţéŕḿš one two]</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_device">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ĥåš ţĥé åɓîļîţý ţö ḿöñîţöŕ åñð ḿåñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕḿîššîöñš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš ðéVîçé, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîVîţý, åš ŵéļļ åš ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý, åñð çöñţåçţ šéåŕçĥ ĥîšţöŕý.&lt;br>&lt;br>Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ƒöŕ ḿöŕé îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîVåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_profile">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ĥåš ţĥé åɓîļîţý ţö ḿöñîţöŕ åñð ḿåñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕḿîššîöñš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîVîţý, åš ŵéļļ åš ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý, åñð çöñţåçţ šéåŕçĥ ĥîšţöŕý.&lt;br>&lt;br>Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ƒöŕ ḿöŕé îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîVåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="app_label">[Ŵöŕķ Šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="back">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="brand_screen_header">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ɓéļöñĝš ţö ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="brand_screen_subheader">[Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð ţö ḿåñåĝé åñð ḿöñîţöŕ ţĥîš þĥöñé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="cancel_delete_profile">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_provisioning">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_msg">[Éñðîñĝ ţĥîš šéţûþ ŵîļļ ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð ţåķé ýöû ɓåçķ ţö ţĥé ƒîŕšţ šçŕééñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_ok">[Ŕéšéţ ðéVîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_and_factory_reset_dialog_title">[Éñð šéţûþ åñð ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ¿ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="cant_add_work_profile">"[Çåñ'ţ åðð ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="cant_replace_or_remove_work_profile">"[Çåñ'ţ ŕéþļåçé öŕ ŕéḿöVé ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="cant_set_up_device">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ðéVîçé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="cant_set_up_profile">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ þŕöƒîļé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="car_ui_preference_switch_off">[Öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_preference_switch_on">[Öñ one]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_restricted_while_driving">[Féåţûŕé ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé ŵĥîļé ðŕîVîñĝ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_scrollbar_page_down_button">[Šçŕöļļ ðöŵñ one two]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_scrollbar_page_up_button">[Šçŕöļļ ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_toolbar_default_search_hint">[Šéåŕçĥ… one two]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_toolbar_menu_item_overflow_title">[ÖVéŕƒļöŵ one two]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_toolbar_menu_item_search_title">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="car_ui_toolbar_menu_item_settings_title">[Šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="change_device_launcher">[Çĥåñĝé ðéVîçé ļåûñçĥéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="close_list">[Çļöšé ļîšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="collapse">[Çöļļåþšé one two]</string>
    <string name="comp_profile_benefits_description">[βý ûšîñĝ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé, ýöû çåñ ķééþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš îñ öñé þļåçé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="company_controls_device">[Ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ ŵîļļ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ðéVîçé åñð ķééþ îţ šéçûŕé. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="company_controls_workspace">[Ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ çöñţŕöļš ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé åñð ķééþš îţ šéçûŕé. Ýöû çöñţŕöļ éVéŕýţĥîñĝ éļšé öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="contact_device_provider">[Ţö ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ %1$s. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="contact_your_admin_for_help">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="contact_your_admin_for_more_info">"[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ƒöŕ ḿöŕé îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîVåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="continue_button">[Çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_text">[Ţåþ ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_title">[Éñçŕýþţîöñ çöḿþļéţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_1_header">"[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé &amp;  ḿåñåĝéð ɓý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_2_header">"[Þéŕšöñåļ åþþš åŕé šéþåŕåţé &amp;  ĥîððéñ ƒŕöḿ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_3_header">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ çåñ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ðéVîçé &amp;  ɓļöçķ çéŕţåîñ åþþš one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_summary">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé åñð ḿåñåĝéð ɓý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. Þéŕšöñåļ åþþš åŕé šéþåŕåţé åñð ĥîððéñ ƒŕöḿ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ çåñ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ðéVîçé åñð ɓļöçķ çéŕţåîñ åþþš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="copy">[Çöþý one]</string>
    <string name="copying_certs">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ÇÅ çéŕţîƒîçåţéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="couldnt_set_up_device">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ðéVîçé. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="cross_profile_consent_summary">[Çöññéçţéð åþþš ļéţ ýöû åççéšš ŵöŕķ åñð þéŕšöñåļ ðåţå ţöĝéţĥéŕ. Ýöû çåñ ḿåķé çĥåñĝéš åñýţîḿé îñ Šéţţîñĝš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="cross_profile_consent_title">"[Çöññéçţ ŵöŕķ &amp;  þéŕšöñåļ åþþš one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="cross_profile_notification_channel_name">"[Çöññéçţ ŵöŕķ &amp;  þéŕšöñåļ åþþš one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="cross_profile_notification_text">[Åççéšš ŵöŕķ åñð þéŕšöñåļ ðåţå ţöĝéţĥéŕ. Ţåþ ţö šéţ ûþ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="cross_profile_notification_title">"[Çöññéçţ ŵöŕķ &amp;  þéŕšöñåļ åþþš one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="default_first_meat_user_name">[Þŕîḿåŕý ûšéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="default_managed_profile_name">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two]</string>
    <string name="default_owned_device_username">[Ûšéŕ öƒ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="delete_profile">[Ðéļéţé one two]</string>
    <string name="delete_profile_title">[Ðéļéţé éхîšţîñĝ þŕöƒîļé¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_already_set_up">[ÐéVîçé îš åļŕéåðý šéţ ûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_doesnt_allow_encryption_contact_admin">"[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ éñçŕýþţîöñ, ŵĥîçĥ îš ñééðéð ƒöŕ šéţûþ. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="device_has_reset_protection_contact_admin">[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ĥåš ŕéšéţ þŕöţéçţîöñ ţûŕñéð öñ. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_cancel_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_cancel_message">"[Šţöþ šéţţîñĝ ûþ åñð éŕåšé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé'š ðåţå¿ one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="device_owner_description">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîļļ ɓé ķéþţ šéçûŕé åñð ḿåñåĝéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_ok">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_info">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð, ḿöñîţöŕéð, åñð ķéþţ šéçûŕé ɓý %1$s. Ţéŕḿš ŵîļļ åþþļý. %2$s one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_info_with_terms_headers">[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð, ḿöñîţöŕéð, åñð ķéþţ šéçûŕé ɓý %1$s. Ţéŕḿš ƒŕöḿ %2$s ŵîļļ åþþļý. %3$s one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]</string>
    <string name="device_provisioning_finished">[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé îš ŕéåðý ţö ĝö¡ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="dismiss">[Ðîšḿîšš one two]</string>
    <string name="done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="downloading_administrator_header">[Ĝéţţîñĝ ŕéåðý ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ šéţûþ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="encrypt">[Éñçŕýþţ one two]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_device_owner_setup">[Ţö šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðéVîçé, îţ ñééðš ţö ɓé éñçŕýþţéð ƒîŕšţ. Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé šöḿé ţîḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_profile_owner_setup">[Ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé, ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ñééðš ţö ɓé éñçŕýþţéð. Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé šöḿé ţîḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_this_device_question">[Éñçŕýþţ ţĥîš ðéVîçé¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="error_download_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="error_hash_mismatch">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ ðûé ţö å çĥéçķšûḿ éŕŕöŕ. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]"</string>
    <string name="error_installation_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ îñšţåļļ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="error_package_invalid">"[Çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ. Îţ'š ḿîššîñĝ çöḿþöñéñţš öŕ çöŕŕûþţéð. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="error_wifi">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî one two three]"</string>
    <string name="expand">[Éхþåñð one two]</string>
    <string name="expand_button_title">[ÅðVåñçéð one two]</string>
    <string name="for_help_contact_admin">[Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="frp_clear_progress_text">[Þļéåšé ŵåîţ... one two three]</string>
    <string name="frp_clear_progress_title">[Éŕåšîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_accept_header">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_privacy_body">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ḿåý ɓé åɓļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîVîţý öñ ţĥîš ðéVîçé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_privacy_title">[ÞŕîVåçý ŕéḿîñðéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_progress_label">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé… one two three]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_1_header">[Ķééþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åţ ýöûŕ ƒîñĝéŕţîþš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_2_header">"[Ţĥîš ðéVîçé îšñ'ţ þŕîVåţé one two three]"</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_2_subheader">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ḿåý ɓé åɓļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîVîţý öñ ţĥîš ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_summary">"[Ûšé ţĥîš ðéVîçé ţö éåšîļý åççéšš ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ţĥîš ðéVîçé îšñ'ţ þŕîVåţé, šö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ ḿåý ɓé åɓļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîVîţý. Ţö ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="if_questions_contact_admin">[Îƒ ýöû ĥåVé Qûéšţîöñš, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="info_anim_title_0">[Çĥåñĝé ţĥé ŵåý ýöû ŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="info_anim_title_1">[Šéþåŕåţé ŵöŕķ ƒŕöḿ þéŕšöñåļ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="info_anim_title_2">"[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŵöŕķ ŵĥéñ ýöû'ŕé ðöñé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="join_many_items_first">[%1$s, %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="join_many_items_last">[%1$s, åñð %2$s one two]</string>
    <string name="join_many_items_middle">[%1$s, %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="join_two_items">[%1$s åñð %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="launcher_app_cant_be_used_by_work_profile">"[Ţĥîš ļåûñçĥéŕ åþþ çåñ'ţ ɓé ûšéð ɓý ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="learn_more_label">[Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé ɓûţţöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_link">[Ļéåŕñ ḿöŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="link_isnt_secure_and_cant_be_opened_until_device_setup_finished">"[Ţĥîš ļîñķ îšñ'ţ šéçûŕé åñð çåñ'ţ ɓé öþéñéð ûñţîļ ðéVîçé šéţûþ îš ƒîñîšĥéð: %1$s one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="managed_device_info">[Ḿåñåĝéð ðéVîçé îñƒö one two three]</string>
    <string name="managed_provisioning_error_text">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţḿéñţ öŕ ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="mdm_icon_label">[%1$s îçöñ one]</string>
    <string name="next">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="not_set">[Ñöţ šéţ one two]</string>
    <string name="now_lets_set_up_everything_else">[Åðð å þéŕšöñåļ åççöûñţ ţö ĝéţ ḿöŕé ƒŕöḿ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="now_lets_set_up_everything_else_explanation">[Ñöŵ ţĥåţ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš ŕéåðý, ýöû çåñ åļšö åðð å þéŕšöñåļ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ţö åççéšš ýöûŕ åþþš åñð çöñţéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="ok_setup">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="one_place_for_work_apps">[Öñé þļåçé ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three]</string>
    <string name="opening_paragraph_delete_profile">"[Ýöû åļŕéåðý ĥåVé å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Îţ'š ḿåñåĝéð ûšîñĝ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ: one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="organization_admin">[ÎŢ åðḿîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="pick_launcher">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="preference_copied">[\"%1$s\" çöþîéð ţö çļîþɓöåŕð. one two three]</string>
    <string name="profile_benefits_description">[βý ûšîñĝ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé, ýöû çåñ šéþåŕåţé ŵöŕķ ðåţå ƒŕöḿ þéŕšöñåļ ðåţå one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_cancel">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_message">[Šţöþ šéţţîñĝ ûþ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_ok">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancelling">[Çåñçéļîñĝ… one two]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_info">"[Ýöû'ŕé åɓöûţ ţö çŕéåţé å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ţĥåţ'ļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð åñð ḿöñîţöŕéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Ţéŕḿš ŵîļļ åþþļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_info_comp">[Å þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ ɓé çŕéåţéð ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé åñð ţĥé ŕéšţ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ŵîļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð åñð ḿöñîţöŕéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Ţéŕḿš ŵîļļ åþþļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_info_with_terms_headers">"[Ýöû'ŕé åɓöûţ ţö çŕéåţé å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ţĥåţ'ļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð åñð ḿöñîţöŕéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Ţéŕḿš ƒŕöḿ %1$s ŵîļļ åþþļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]"</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_info_with_terms_headers_comp">[Å þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ ɓé çŕéåţéð ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé åñð ţĥé ŕéšţ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ŵîļļ ɓé ḿåñåĝéð åñð ḿöñîţöŕéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ. Ţéŕḿš ƒŕöḿ %1$s ŵîļļ åþþļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen]</string>
    <string name="progress_connect_to_mobile_network">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="progress_connect_to_wifi">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö Ŵî-Fî… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_data_process">[Þŕöçéššîñĝ šéţûþ ðåţå… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_delete_non_required_apps">[ŔéḿöVîñĝ ñöñ-ŕéQûîŕéð šýšţéḿ åþþš… one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="progress_download">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="progress_finishing_touches">[Þûţţîñĝ ƒîñîšĥîñĝ ţöûçĥéš… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="progress_initialize">[Îñîţîåļîžîñĝ ðéVîçé… one two three]</string>
    <string name="progress_install">[Îñšţåļļîñĝ ţĥé åðḿîñ åþþ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="progress_set_owner">[Šéţţîñĝ ţĥé ðéVîçé öŵñéŕ… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="provisioning">[ÞŕöVîšîöñîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="provisioning_error_title">[Ööþš¡ one]</string>
    <string name="read_more_delete_profile">[βéƒöŕé þŕöçééðîñĝ, <a href="#read_this_link">ŕéåð ţĥîš</a>. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="read_terms">[Ŕéåð ţéŕḿš one two]</string>
    <string name="reset">[Ŕéšéţ one]</string>
    <string name="reset_device">[Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðéVîçé åñð ţŕý šéţţîñĝ îţ ûþ åĝåîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">[Šéåŕçĥ one two]</string>
    <string name="section_content">[%1$s šéçţîöñ çöñţéñţ: %2$s one two three]</string>
    <string name="section_heading">[%1$s šéçţîöñ ĥéåðîñĝ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="set_up_everything_else">[Šéţ ûþ éVéŕýţĥîñĝ éļšé one two three]</string>
    <string name="set_up_your_device">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setting_up_workspace">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_device">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="setup_isnt_finished_contact_admin">"[Šéţûþ îšñ'ţ ƒîñîšĥéð. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="setup_profile">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="setup_provisioning_header">[Þŕéþåŕîñĝ ţö šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_provisioning_header_description">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ åðḿîñ åþþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_device">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ŵöŕķ ðéVîçé… one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_profile">[Šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">[Šöḿéţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">[999+ one]</string>
    <string name="stop_setup_reset_device_question">"[Šţöþ šéţûþ &amp;  ŕéšéţ ðéVîçé¿ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="sud_back_button_label">[βåçķ one]</string>
    <string name="sud_more_button_label">[Ḿöŕé one]</string>
    <string name="sud_next_button_label">[Ñéхţ one]</string>
    <string name="summary_collapsed_preference_list">[%1$s, %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="sure_you_want_to_delete_profile">[Îƒ ýöû çöñţîñûé, åļļ åþþš åñð ðåţå îñ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ ɓé ðéļéţéð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="take_a_few_minutes">[Ţĥîš ḿåý ţåķé å ƒéŵ ḿîñûţéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="terms">[Ţéŕḿš one]</string>
    <string name="the_following_is_your_mdm">[Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ ñééð ţö åççéšš ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé: one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="the_following_is_your_mdm_for_device">[Ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ ŵîļļ ḿåñåĝé ýöûŕ ðéVîçé: one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="theft_protection_disabled_warning">[Ţö ûšé ţĥéƒţ-þŕöţéçţîöñ ƒéåţûŕéš, ýöû ḿûšţ ĥåVé å þåššŵöŕð-þŕöţéçţéð šçŕééñ ļöçķ ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="this_will_reset_take_back_first_screen">[Ţĥîš ŵîļļ ŕéšéţ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð ţåķé ýöû ɓåçķ ţö ţĥé ƒîŕšţ šçŕééñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="url_error">[Ţĥîš ļîñķ çåññöţ ɓé ðîšþļåýéð. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="user_consent_msg">[Î çöñšéñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="user_setup_incomplete">[Ûšéŕ Šéţûþ Îñçöḿþļéţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="v7_preference_off">[ÖFF one]</string>
    <string name="v7_preference_on">[ÖÑ one]</string>
    <string name="view_terms">[νîéŵ ţéŕḿš one two]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_cant_be_added_contact_admin">[Å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé çåñ’ţ ɓé åððéð ţö ţĥîš ðéVîçé. Îƒ ýöû ĥåVé Qûéšţîöñš, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_description">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ ɓé ķéþţ îñ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé åñð ḿåñåĝéð ɓý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_info">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îñƒö one two three]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_accept_header">"[Fîŕšţ, ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_accept_header_post_suw">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_progress_label">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_1_header">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_2_header">"[Þåûšé ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû'ŕé ðöñé ƒöŕ ţĥé ðåý one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_3_header">[Ðåţå îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš Vîšîɓļé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_summary">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Ýöû çåñ þåûšé ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû’ŕé ðöñé ƒöŕ ţĥé ðåý. Ţĥé ðåţå îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš Vîšîɓļé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðḿîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_later_message">"[Ýöû çåñ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ļåţéŕ îñ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š ðéVîçé ḿåñåĝéḿéñţ åþþ one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_later_title">[Šţöþ þŕöƒîļé šéţûþ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_stop">[Šţöþ one]</string>
    <string name="your_org_app_used">[%1$s ŵîļļ ḿåñåĝé åñð ḿöñîţöŕ ţĥîš ðéVîçé ûšîñĝ ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ åþþ: one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="your_organization_beginning">[Ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="your_organization_middle">[ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three]</string>
</resources>
